tolmol.com 2011-06-09

# Privacy policy | TolMol.com

##### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information (PII) may be requested.

##### TolMol's Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to the services offered by TolMol website located at http://www.tolmol.com and directly associated domains (collectively, "TolMol Site" or "Website"), including any features, content, or applications offered from time to time by TolMol (collectively, the "TolMol Services"). The TolMol Services are hosted in the United States. By using TolMol Services, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.

This privacy policy is incorporated into and is subject to the TolMol[Terms of Use.](http://www.tolmol.com/terms-of-use) Your use of the TolMol Site and any personal information you provide on the Website remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our [Terms of Use.](http://www.tolmol.com/terms-of-use)

Please note that any video, image, comment or other content posted on the Website becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information which is subject to this Privacy Policy.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By using or accessing TolMol Site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

##### The Information We Collect From You:

We collect only such information from you as necessary to provide services to you from the TolMol. When you visit TolMol Site you provide us with two types of information: personally identifiable information (PII) you knowingly choose to share that is collected by us and Webwite use information collected by us as you interact with our Web Site.

When you register as a Member of TolMol, you voluntarily provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your telephone number, your mailing address, your gender, school or college attended and any other personal or preference information that you choose to provide to us. The TolMol Site is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect PII from children under 16 (sixteen) years of age. If you are a parent of a child under the age of sixteen and you have questions about our Website or Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at support@tolmol.com.

When you visit TolMol Site, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends. This may include information such as your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." Cookies are small bits of information that we place on your computer. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to TolMol Site. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.

When you use the TolMol Site, we may employ "clear GIFs" (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users / members anonymously. In addition, we may also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients.

When you use the TolMol Site, you may set up your personal profile, form connections, send messages to other users, perform searches and queries, create and join communities, add or use applications, and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your friend list. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information.

You post User Content (as defined in the TolMol[Terms of Use](http://www.tolmol.com/terms-of-use)) on the Site at your own risk. Although you can set privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on TolMol Site is a violation of the TolMol Terms of Use and should be reported to support@tolmol.com.

If you decide to use our invitation service to tell a friend about the TolMol Site, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email or instant message inviting him or her to visit the site. TolMol Site stores this information to send this one-time invitation, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at support@tolmol.com to request that we remove this information from our database. 

We may also use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

The TolMol Site includes links to other websites and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website or purchase third party products or services through the TolMol Site, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services. Once you leave TolMol Site via such a link, access a third party application or click on an advertisement, you should verify from the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine, among other things, how they will handle any PII they collect from you.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. Please note that the TolMol does not sell or rent your Personal Information to anyone.

When a Member who is located in the European Union chooses to post Profile Information that will be publicly disclosed, that Member is responsible for ensuring that such information conforms to all local data protection laws. TolMol is not responsible under the EU local data protection laws for Member-posted information.

Please also note that as our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that we sell some or all of our assets, or the TolMol Site is acquired by another company, information about our visitors may be among the transferred assets.

##### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Our internal security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our users.

##### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access and update all your personally identifiable information that we collect online by logging in to your TolMol account by providing user id and secure password. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

##### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at support@tolmol.com.

We may change or supplement this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any material changes in the way TolMol uses personally identifiable information will be described in future versions of this Privacy Policy. Privacy Policy changes will apply to the information collected from the date we post the revised Privacy Policy, as well as to existing information held by us.

By providing you with this Privacy Policy Statement, TolMol is pledging our continued commitment to protecting the information you provide us. TolMol regularly examines our information privacy practices to determine whether we are adhering to the disclosures about the collection, use, sharing, and protection of your personally identifiable information made in this privacy statement.
